* India

==================================================

A KEYWORD RESEARCH SEO COMPANY

    * [Content Writing Company in India | Premium Copywriting agency](https://contentspotlight.org/content-writing-company-in-india-premium-copywriting-agency/)
    * [Content Writing Services in India | Trustworthy Editorial services](https://contentspotlight.org/content-writing-services-in-india-trustworthy-editorial-services/)
    * [Content Writing Services in Kolkata | Best Copywriting Agency](https://contentspotlight.org/content-writing-services-in-kolkata-best-copywriting-agency/)

PRIVACY POLICY
--------------

[SEO Company in India](https://contentspotlight.org/) » **PRIVACY POLICY**

Who we are
----------

**Suggested text:** We are a content marketing and SEO company and our website address is: [https://contentspotlight.org](https://contentspotlight.org/).

Comments
--------

**Suggested text:** When visitors leave comments on the site, we collect the data shown in the comments form including name, email address and website name to help spam detection.

Embedded content from other websites
------------------------------------

**Suggested text:** Articles on this site may include embedded content (e.g. videos, images, articles, etc.). Embedded content from other websites behaves in the exact same way as if the visitor has visited the other website.

These websites may collect data about you, use cookies, embed additional third-party tracking, and monitor your interaction with that embedded content, including tracking your interaction with the embedded content if you have an account and are logged in to that website.

How long we retain your data
----------------------------

**Suggested text:** If you leave a comment, the comment and its metadata are retained indefinitely. This is so we can recognize and approve any follow-up comments automatically instead of holding them in a moderation queue.

For users that register on our website (if any), we also store the personal information they provide in their user profile. Website administrators can also see and edit that information.

What rights you have over your data
-----------------------------------

**Suggested text:** If you have an account on this site, or have left comments, you can request to receive an exported file of the personal data we hold about you, including any data you have provided to us. You can also request that we erase any personal data we hold about you. We do not send your personal data to anyone. This does not include any data we are obliged to keep for administrative, legal, or security purposes.

### Share this:

### Like this:

Like Loading...

Copyright © Content Spotlight 2023
----------------------------------

### Web Safety

BOSS

### Free of toxic links

Approved by [Sur.ly](https://sur.ly/)

2023

[

](https://www.designrush.com/)

Address: 563 Jessore Road, Kolkata - 700074, West Bengal, India

Email: info@contentspotlight.org

Phone: +91-9831405832

SEO Cornerstone
---------------

[

](https://contentspotlight.org/top-seo-company-in-india-best-seo-services/ "Top SEO Company in India | Bes… on CONTENT SPOTLIGHT")

[

](https://contentspotlight.org/cro-focused-seo-services-in-kolkata-seo-company-in-kolkata/ "CRO focused SEO Services in Ko… on CONTENT SPOTLIGHT")

[

](https://contentspotlight.org/best-seo-company-in-kolkata-reliable-seo-services/ "Best SEO Company in Kolkata| R… on CONTENT SPOTLIGHT")

[

](https://contentspotlight.org/seo-agency-in-kolkata-in-2023-roi-focused-seo-company/ "SEO Agency in Kolkata in 2023… on CONTENT SPOTLIGHT")

[

](https://contentspotlight.org/seo-agency-in-india-cro-focused-seo-company/ "SEO Agency in India | CRO focu… on CONTENT SPOTLIGHT")

[

](https://contentspotlight.org/seo-services-in-india-trustworthy-seo/ "SEO Services in India | Trustw… on CONTENT SPOTLIGHT")

[

](https://contentspotlight.org/best-seo-agency-in-kolkata-top-seo-agency/ "Best SEO Agency in Kolkata | T… on CONTENT SPOTLIGHT")

[

](https://contentspotlight.org/best-seo-services-in-kolkata-leading-seo-service-provider/ "Best SEO services in Kolkata |… on CONTENT SPOTLIGHT")

[

](https://contentspotlight.org/top-seo-company-in-kolkata-best-seo-agency/ "Top SEO Company in Kolkata | B… on CONTENT SPOTLIGHT")

[

](https://contentspotlight.org/best-seo-company-in-india-top-seo-agency/ "Best SEO Company in India | To… on CONTENT SPOTLIGHT")

[

](https://contentspotlight.org/best-seo-agency-in-india-premium-seo-services/ "Best SEO agency in India | Pre… on CONTENT SPOTLIGHT")

[

](https://contentspotlight.org/best-seo-services-in-india-enterprise-seo-agency/ "Best SEO services in India | E… on CONTENT SPOTLIGHT")

Important Links
---------------

Copyright © Content Spotlight 2024 All Rights Reserved.

Close

Font Resize

A- A+

Clear cookies

Close

error: Content is protected !!

Manage Cookie Consent

To provide the best experiences, we use technologies like cookies to store and/or access device information. Consenting to these technologies will allow us to process data such as browsing behavior or unique IDs on this site. Not consenting or withdrawing consent, may adversely affect certain features and functions.

Functional  Functional Always active

The technical storage or access is strictly necessary for the legitimate purpose of enabling the use of a specific service explicitly requested by the subscriber or user, or for the sole purpose of carrying out the transmission of a communication over an electronic communications network.

Preferences  Preferences

The technical storage or access is necessary for the legitimate purpose of storing preferences that are not requested by the subscriber or user.

Statistics  Statistics

The technical storage or access that is used exclusively for statistical purposes. The technical storage or access that is used exclusively for anonymous statistical purposes. Without a subpoena, voluntary compliance on the part of your Internet Service Provider, or additional records from a third party, information stored or retrieved for this purpose alone cannot usually be used to identify you.

Marketing  Marketing

The technical storage or access is required to create user profiles to send advertising, or to track the user on a website or across several websites for similar marketing purposes.

Accept Deny View preferences Save preferences [View preferences](#)

Manage consent

%d
